I consistently find it fascinating that it doesn't matter how long I have been out here being the same person, like a person of character and principle, that there is still people that will question my decisions even before they see the outcome.
I find it utterly fascinating, truly though. And I don't know what that's about, but I just wanted to come on here to remind y'all, I'm like a really, really, really, really, really, really smart person.
And even more than that, I am a really generous person. And like people are seeing a picture with me and Tasha Kay and are losing their minds.
And I find it fascinating, truly. But I also understand that, you know, folks live in a kind of silo that I don't live in, right?
So they carry, they carry folks. They carry weight around folks. They are committed to folks in a way that I am not.
And that's whether it's Tasha Kay or Jasmine Crockett. I am committed to my principles. You know, I'm committed to my principles.
And my principles have some very basic guidelines. Come at me correctly. Show up authentically. And be respectful. You know, be respectful.
And when I went on Funky Dineva the first time, it was very similar.
Why would you do that? And I think it's also really odd to me that you all don't realize that, like, there are silos of folks.
There are people who never hear from other people, from other voices, because we are so cordoned into these spaces of our algorithm
that we don't get to hear other people, that we don't get to hear other points of view.
And so it takes action to actually break those silos.
It takes literal consciousness and initiative to be proactive and, like, cut through those walls.
And what I need people to think about more often is that there is a bigger picture of actual human beings
that are being reached beyond the individual in front of you.
So when I was on Jubilee, people had an issue with me doing Jubilee, because they didn't like Jubilee.
However, it wasn't about Jubilee.
It was about reaching an audience that needed to hear what was being said.
And that happened.
And what a lot of people don't understand is that it's not even that the audience that I was looking to reach
were the people that I was talking to.
No.
The audience that I was looking to reach was so many people who don't realize that those people exist.
They don't even realize that the indoctrination has gotten this far.
I'm really, really smart.
And I am not a selfish person.
And so I think it's important to understand how you see certain people move.
Because it also just alleviates, like, stress.
Like, sometimes I feel like y'all are taking on, like, opinions and, like, really strong opinions and stress
about shit that's, like, not even what you think it is.
But then you don't apply that to shit that really should be stressing you out, right?
So there's spaces that I won't go into because I don't see any value in those spaces.
And that could be because of the actual individual.
That could be because of their audience.
And that could be because of their messaging.
I also know that there are spaces that I can go into, but that I have to actually have a consciousness about.
And then there are spaces that I can go into.
And I actually don't.
Like, I can go on Monet Exchanges' show.
And, you know, we just gonna have a key.
Right?
We just gonna have a key.
But I know that if I go into a space with a host like Tasha Kay or Funky Dyniva,
I'm gonna have to have a consciousness in that space because I know that they are a type of interviewer
and that their audience is very responsive to certain behaviors that, like, they like tea.
And I don't want to be a part of tea.
So I know I have to have a consciousness around that.
But there's other spaces that I just won't go into at all anymore because they don't have a consciousness about me.
Like, I'm not gonna go on mainstream media anymore because they don't have a consciousness about me.
Right?
I'm not gonna go on right-wing spaces because they don't have a consciousness about me.
The only reason I went on Shannon Sharp's show is because I was lied to and told that it would be a safe space.
Had I not been told that, I wouldn't have gone.
So I think it's really necessary to understand, for instance, why, like, I wouldn't go on The Breakfast Club again.
I wouldn't go on The Breakfast Club again because that's not a space that I consider to be,
I don't even know, I don't consider that to be a safe space anymore.
Like, I don't rock with Charlemagne.
And just as a space, I know that I can't go on there and say what I want to say because it's corporate media.
So I can't go in there and speak how I speak.
I have to go in spaces where the person there is in control of the space.
Because the things that I'm saying are the things that are exposing who is in control and how they are disregarding us, how they are oppressing us, etc.
So I have to choose when I'm going to go into a space where I know that me being in that space is going to be a capitalizing moment for that other person.
However, where I also know that symbiotically, it's not going to be capitalizing for me in terms of money,
but it can be useful in terms of bringing education to folks who don't necessarily get access to that.
And I have been on, someone's asking here, would you do Joy Reid or Don Lemon?
I've been on Don Lemon's show.
I would not go on Joy Reid's show.
I do not trust her.
As for Don Lemon, I mean, I don't know that it would be useful at this point,
but, um, I don't see why not.
Someone said,
But you know Jasmine Crockett follows you.
Do you not think she values and identify with a lot of the same views you have?
There are videos that she says she does not take money from APAC.
Jasmine Crockett has not at any point denounced Israel or the genocide.
I'm not sure what's difficult about that.
Like, I don't understand what you all don't see about that.
At no point has she said,
I am vehemently against this genocide.
I will not support it.
She has actually said,
I have sent money and I will continue to send money.
So, like, why is this confusing for you?
Why is this confusing for you?
This is not confusing for me.
This is a very clear issue for me.
Israel supports the genocide.
Israel is an apartheid state.
Israel supports sending weapons to Haiti to keep it destabilized.
Israel supported sending weapons to Guatemala to kill indigenous people.
Israel supports sending weapons to Sudan to continue to support the destabilization there.
And Israel is raping the Congo.
Like, what are we talking about?
And that's just one of my issues.
So stop.
Stop playing dumb and stop even suggesting that she's playing dumb.
Because that's just disingenuous.
Stop.
I just said spaces that I trust.
Spaces that I trust are spaces where the person who is interviewing me actually runs the space.
Spaces where they are genuinely welcoming me into the space.
And I know that, and we don't have any history of them being shady.
So even if Tasha Kay is, like, funny style in, like, a gossipy way, like, I don't have any shady history with her.
So, you know, that's how it goes.
Yes, there are many spaces like that.
Sabby Sabs.
Breakthrough News.
The Tea with Miriam Francois.
Palestine Pod.
Brianna Joy Gray.
Nico House.
I can go on and on and on.
What are we talking about?
Sovereign Media.
You know, that's the thing that is so kind of frustrating about communicating with you all a lot of times is because you know for yourself that you haven't done any research about something, but you will consciously speak to its limitations.
That's weird to me.
Why would Native Land Podcast be a safe space for me?
It's not a safe space for me.
So, I have been in this space for a long time.
And when I say the space, I mean a public-facing person.
So, I have history with a lot of people.
Positive, negative, and then some people that don't have history at all.
Why do I keep talking down to your audience?
Because I want you to level up.
And the folks who are leveled up do not feel offended when I speak like that because they know I'm not talking to them.
So, if you felt like I was talking to you, that is you being a hit dog and hollering.
And I did not call you my audience uneducated.
What I said was, so often you all speak to things that you know you haven't researched and you then call it limitations.
That makes no sense.
Do not talk to me about things you have not researched with confidence.
Think before you speak.
It's called an ultra-crepidarian.
I got to look that up.
An ultra-crepidarian.
I'm not going to apologize because I meant what I said.
You took it the way that you took it because you are insecure.
So, no, I'm not going to apologize.
And you're about to get cut.
But, thank you to Houston.
We had a great evening.
It was so beautiful.
Shout out to Las Peras for bringing us into the space.
And Andrea for bringing us into the space.
We had a really beautiful time.
Tomorrow, we'll be in New Orleans at Baldwin & Co. Books.
So, shout out to the folks over there and DJ.
And then we will be in Atlanta on Saturday.
So, I hope you guys get your RSVPs in for Atlanta.
Because Atlanta was definitely not showing love in the way that I thought they would.
And I hope that they will.
And shout out to Auburn Research Library because it's going to be great.
And I'm really excited to be in that space.
And then on Dele's, on Sunday, I'll be in Dele's.
So, shout out to Dele's and Pan-African Connection Bookstore.
And so, it's been really cool to have all these spaces bringing us in.
And really just being so welcoming to what is necessary.
Being so welcoming to the messaging that I'm bringing to the space.
And understanding the importance of it.
So, big ups to everybody who comes through with an open mind, open heart, with curiosity.
Like genuine curiosity and compassion.
Because that's really what it requires.
And the best part is seeing y'all exchange information and create community after these gatherings.
Like that to me is the best part.
Like when I see y'all connecting and making new plans.
And, you know, carrying forth the community beyond.
Because I am a conduit, right?
So, what happens is I am a conduit.
You know what?
I'm just going to block this guy because he's annoying.
So, let me just block him.
Um, I am a conduit for bringing people together.
And that's why it's really important that I don't have alliance with like organizations.
Or, um, like I'm not trapped in certain limitations that happen when you are aligned.
Um, aligned is not the word.
Because I am aligned with organizations and people.
But I'm not, um, I don't know.
Like I'm just not limited by those alignments.
I would love to come to Jacksonville.
Shout out to Duval.
Um, and so it's really cool when I get to see.
Also, all of these, uh, stops have been really different.
So, I'm going to keep doing them and, um, my best, doing my best to get to as many, uh, places and spaces as possible.
And, yeah, I'm a weaver, a spider.
I love spiders.
Um, and just continue to, um, to try my best to find ways to bring us together.
How do you vote if you don't have an agreeable candidate?
Not vote?
I mean, at this point, that's how I feel.
And I feel like if there was actually a movement around withholding a vote like there was during the election, there would be something very real that starts to happen.
But the reality is that folks are so afraid to make drastic change.
And they somehow think that if they just continue to do the same thing over and over and over again, that they will get a different result.
Which Confucius has actually said is the sign of insanity.
So, um, I don't care who they come for me.
Who's going to come for me?
Nobody reputable is coming for me.
I'll tell you that.
Thank you, Wendegard.
I've been doing Patreon lives of the different stops on the book tours.
That's been really cool.
Um, so here we have someone named IamLisha underscore B.
Not voting is not the answer.
Someone is going to run this country.
So, um, the United States has inflicted and infringed and interjected.
Interjected is not the word.
Has, um, has...
I can't think of the words because I'm tired.
But the United States has infringed upon elections all over the world for at least the last 60 years.
Intervened.
Thank you.
It is currently doing so in Honduras, where they are actively buying the vote of the individuals in Honduras.
In Honduras.
They pardoned.
I don't even know how you do this, but they pardoned a narco trafficker.
They pardoned a Honduran drug trafficker.
So you know how they're telling you that they're killing folks in Venezuela because they're trafficking drugs in the United States?
They just pardoned a drug trafficker in Honduras who is in support of the person that they want in power to be their puppet.
So, I have no idea why so many of you all think that the United States that continues to infiltrate and intervene in elections all over the world is giving you a fair election at home.
I just, I just, I just, I just can't understand it.
The same way that I can't understand why you all think me who lives in facts should have a conversation with any individual that does not live in facts.
I, I, I don't understand what you all seem to think is going on, but that's not a thing.
So, um, again, this idea that if you just keep doing things the same way that you're gonna get a different result is nonsensical.
It's impractical. It's impractical. Literally, it's impractical.
Like you, you consistently think that if you, that you will vote your way out of things that you cannot possibly believe will change with a vote.
We are literally in fascism. Literally.
And y'all are talking about if we just vote for this black lady who don't got no policies, something's gonna change.
Are you nuts? Are you nuts?
We haven't even had this administration in office for a year and y'all are talking about midterms.
I, I just, I, I, I can't, um, I can't make it make sense.
I can't make it make sense.
So I will continue to do the work that I do, which is the work of decolonizing.
Um, I will continue to try my best to just really give you all as much information as possible.
And also encourage you to actually do your best to synthesize that information into action without me having to hold your hand and walk you to action.
Because that is actually doing you a disservice.
Good night, y'all.